Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory01
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents A
  - Angell, James R. (Box 2)
    - Woodworth, R.S. -- from Boas (see), 1931 Sept 2
  - Anglo-American University Library for Central Europe (Box 2)
    - Prelim. Statement, 1920 Mar. 31; 3p
    - Prelim. Statement, 1920 Apr.; 3p
    - Printed doc., 1920 May 31; 3p
    - Uncorrected proof, 1920 July
      Also see Headicar, B.M. and Skillings, Everett
  - Angoff, Charles (Box 2)
    - To Boas, 1934 June 28; 1p
  - Angulo, Jaime de (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 June 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 May 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 July 2; 2p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 July 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 July 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1932 Sept 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 June 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 June 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Aug. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 June 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 29; 23p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 18; 5p
    - To Boas, 1927 June 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 13; 5p
    - To Boas, 1927 July 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec.?; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 31; 4p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 4; 2p
    - (probably from J.deA), 1928 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Jan. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec.?; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 1; 1p
    - (see From Boas), 1930 Mar. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sep 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 28; 6p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 6
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct 9
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct 20
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct 21
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov 2
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov 6
    - (on margin of FB letter of Nov. 28), 1932 Nov?
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec 31
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr 18
    - To Boas, 1933 June 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 6
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug 23
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 31
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr 9
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug 25
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec 5
    - (see From Boas), 1937 May 12
    - To Boas, 1939 July 29
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb 23
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar 24
    - To Boas, 1942 June 12
    - To Boas, 1942 June 29
    - (see Edel, B.C.), 1942 June 17
    - Edel, B.C. -- from J. deA, 1942 June 29
  - Angulo, Mrs. Lucy Freeland (Box 3)
  - Anita (Box 3)
    see Brenner, Anita
  - Ankermann, B. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov 20
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec 31
    - To Boas, 1923 Jul 24
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan 31
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan 18
  - Anon. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1882 Aug 21
    - From Boas, 1888 Feb 9
    - From Boas, 1905 May 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 May 19
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan?
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec?; 5p
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec?
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec?
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar 8
    - From Boas, 1917 June 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug 16; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec 18
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb 28; 8p
      - re Swetlow, 1928 Dec?
      - re Olson, 1928 Dec?
      - re Cronberg, 1929 Aug 1; 2p
    - From Boas, 1932 Aug 9
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec?
    - From Boas, 1935 Nov 27
    - From Boas, 1935 Dec?; 4p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan 2
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec?; 3p
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep?; 2p
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec?
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan 5
    - To Boas, 1883
    - To Boas, 1885 Nov 20
    - To Boas, 1887 Apr 1
    - To Boas, 1889 Feb 26
      - re Newell, 1907 Mar 10; 4p
    - To Boas, 1913 Sep 30
    - To Boas, 1916 Sep 12
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr?
    - To Boas, 1917 Dec?; 6p
      - re: M. Magnus, 1920 Dec?; 3p
    - To Boas, 1921 May 24
    - To Boas, 1921 Jun 17
    - To Boas, 1921 Jul 6
    - To Boas, 1921 Jul 11
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct 25
    - To Boas, 1927 May 7
    - To Boas, 1928 Jun 28
    - To Boas, 1929 Jun?
    - To Boas, 1933 May 13; 5p
    - To Boas, 1933 Jul 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec?
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec?; 2p
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan 24
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar 10
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb 11
      - financial statement, 1939 Aug?
    - To Archaeol. Inst. of Am., 1909 Dec?; 3p
  - [N.M. Butler?]: (Box 3)
    - To Butley, M.M., 1915 Jun 30
    - To Sophie Boas, 1907 Sep 27
    - From Giese, P., 1931 Jul 8
    - To Gulkowitsch, L., 1935 Dec 25; 4p
    - Herz Jesu Missionhaus, 1921 Feb 8
  - [Anonymous] -- (cont'd) (Box 3)
    - To Lips, 1933 Apr. 28; 2p
    - To Mond, Robt., 1937 Mar. 5; 2p
    - To Osborn, 1915 Dec.?; 2p
    - To Petrullo, V., 1935 Sept. 10; 5p
    - To Poland, A.B., 1909 Dec.?; 1p
    - To Roosevelt, F.D, 1939 Dec.?; 1p
    - To Rothe, Erich, 1934 Aug. 10; 1p
    - To Trachtenberg, 1916 May 25; 6p
    - To U.S. President, Sec'y of State, Congress, 1938 May 13; 2p
    - To Waldman, Morris D., 1937 June 3; 2p
    - To Whom It May Concern, 1937 Dec. 18; 1p
    - X-ray stoay, 1939 May 3; 1p
  - Ansah, M.E. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 May 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Dec. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 18; 1p
  - Anshen, Ruth Nanda (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 4; 1p
  - Anthony, L.P. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 28; 1p
  - Anthropological Ass'n (Box 3)
    - from Mason, O.T., 1888 Jan. 3
    - from Brinton,D.G., 1888 Jan. 27
    - from Bolton, H.C., 1888 Jan. 31
    - from Daly, E.P., 1888 Feb. 12
  - Anthropological Journal (Box 3)
    - 1898 Feb. 18
    - Report, 1898 June 15; 2p
    - Report, 1898 July 11; 2p
  - Anthropological Society of Bombay (Box 3)
    - See Thoothi, N.A., 1936 June 18
    - See Thoothi, N.A., 1936 Aug. 3
  - Anthropol. Soc. of Washington (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1898 Nov. 22; 2p
    - (to W. Flint), 1898 Dec. 1; 1p
    - (to P.S. Pierce), 1902 Feb. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 May 25; 2p
    - (from W. Flint), 1898 Nov. 25; 1p
    - List of Foreign Members, 3p
    - (from P.B. Pierce), 1900 Apr. 10; 1p
    - (from P.B. Pierce), 1900 Aug. 6; 1p
    - (from P.B. Pierce), 1900 Oct. 8; 1p
    - (from P.B. Pierce), 1900 Nov. 14; 1p
    - (from P.B. Pierce), 1901 May 21; 1p
    - (from P.B. Pierce), 1901 Aug. 29; 1p
    - Resolution, 1919 Dec. 26; 2p
      (see Mussey, H.R.)
  - Anthropologische Gesellschaft, Wien (Box 3)
    - (from F. Heger), 1890 Mar. 27; 2p
  - Anthrop. Gess., Berlin (Box 3)
    - 1898 May 4
  - Anthropologist -- (American?) (Box 3)
    - (from Henshaw, H.W.), 1888 Mar. 23
  - Anthropology, List of Doctors in (Box 3)
    - 1932 [?] Jan. 30
  - Anti-alien Bills (Box 3)
    - see Anon. to FDR, 1939 Dec.?
  - Anti-Ism League of America (Box 3)
    - Program (see Jackson, A.G.), 1939 June 10
  - Anti-Nazi League, Non-Sectarian to Champion Human Rights (Box 3)
    - To Boas, [?] 1927 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 July 13; 1p.
  - Antisemitism (Box 3)
    - Boas paper, 1933 Dec. 31; 2p.
    - See Teneromo, I., 1911 Dec.?
    - See Shatzky, Jacob, 1939 Feb. 15
  - Antonacchio, F. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 23
    - To Boas, 1908 Nov. 20
  - Apfelbaum, P.M. (Box 3)
    - see Prager, W.L., 1933 May 25
  - Apotheker-Zeituny (Box 3)
    - 1920 Dec.
  - Appasamy, A.J. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 29
  - Appleget, T.B. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Fackenthal, F.D., 1934 Jan. 23
    - From Fackenthal, F.D., 1935 Mar. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 6
    - To Boas, 1898 Mar. 5; 1p
  - Applezweig, Norman (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 29; 1p
  - Aptheker, Herbert (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1941 May 13; 1p
  - Arbib-Costa, A. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 29; 1p
  - Archaeological Inst. of Am. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 24; 2p
    - From Anon., 1909 Dec.?
    - Bulletin, School, 1908 Apr.?; 3p
      see Whicher, G.M.
  - Archives Internationales d'Ethnographic (Box 3)
    - From Kern & Schmeltz, 1894 Feb. 12; 1p
  - Arctic Ethnology (Box 3)
    - see Birket-Smith, K., 1936 May 4
  - Arctowski, J. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1916 June 23
    - To Boas, 1916 July 6
    - To Boas, 1916 July 13
  - Argus Pressclipping Bureau (Box 3)
    - 1905 Dec. 12, 1p
  - Aristogenic Ass'n (Box 3)
    - see Crampton, C.W., 1931 May 22
  - Arlt, G.O. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 11; 1p
  - Arluck, E. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 20; 1p
  - Armer, L.A. (Box 3)
    - To Boas (see J.S. Guggenheim Foun.), 1929 Dec.?
    - see Armer, S., 1934 Oct. 9
  - Armer, S. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 9; 1p
  - Armstrong, Edward C. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1926 May 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Jan. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 19; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 June 18
    - To Boas, 1927 Jan. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 17; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 19; 1p
    - To Goddard, 1927 June 15; 1p
    - To Goddard, 1927 June 18; 1p
  - Armstrong, L.O. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 21; 2p
  - Armstrong, J.S., Jr. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 14
  - Armstrong? Nat.? (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 27
  - Army Medical Museum (Box 3)
    - To Boas from J.S.Billings, 1887 May 14
    - To Boas from J.S.Billings, 1887 Apr 23
  - Arnett, T. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1930 May 16; 2p
    - Arnett -- to A. Flexner, 1927 Nov. 14; 1p
  - Arni,? (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1903 June 16
    - To Boas, 1903 June 16
    - To Boas, 1903 July 21
  - Arnold, C. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 20
  - Arnold, Thurman (Box 3)
    - see Brooks, V.W., 1938 Nov. 22
  - Arntchen, D.W. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 17
  - Aronson, M.J. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 3
    - To Boas, 1935 Sept. 26; 1p
  - Aronstein, Fritz (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 4; 1p
  - Aronstein, Ida (geb. Kaufmann) (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1938 Sept. 10; 4p
  - Arordwski?, A. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec.?; 1p
  - Arrejado Lisboa. M. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 10; 1p
  - Artberg (Artberry?), R. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1915 Oct. 4
  - Art in America (Box 3)
    See Sherman, F.F.
  - Arthur, G.R. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1930 May 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 12; 2p
  - Arthur, Helen (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 9; 1p
  - Artucio, Hugo Fernandez (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Mar. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 6; 1p
  - Artune, F.S. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 28; 1p
  - Asadowskomu, M. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct.?; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 15; 2p
  - Asakawa (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 6
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 17
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 25
  - Asapansa-Johnson, C. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1930,Jan. 31; 4p
    - To Boas, 1930, Apr. 3; 2p
  - Asch, Solomon (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1939 Nov. 13; 1p
  - Aschoff, Ludwig (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 June 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 July 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Aug. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1922 Nov. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 June 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 19; 4p
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 22; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 24; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 July 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 19; 2p
  - Ascoli, Max (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 31; 1p
  - Asfendierow, S. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 28; 1p
  - Ashenden, C. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 27; 1p
  - Ashenhurst (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1905 Oct. 2
  - Ashley, M.E. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1926 June 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 July 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 July 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Sept 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Oct. 19; 2p
  - Ashley-Montagu, M.F. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 3; op
    - From Boas, 1939 Mar. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Oct. 6; 1p
    - see Boas, F., 1942 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 22; 1p
    - A-M -- to Miss Jacobs, 1937 Aug. 16; 1p
  - Ashworth, Robert A. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 30; 1p
  - Asofsky, I.L. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1933 Aug. 25; 1p
  - Associated Musicians of Greater N.Y. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1939 May 29; 1p
  - Ass'n Canadienne Francaise pour L'Avancement des Sciences (Box 3)
    see Rousseau, Jacques
  - Ass'n for the Relief of Needy Physicians of Central & Eastern Europe (Box 3)
    - 1925 July 9
      enc. with Bopp, W.F.
  - Ass'n of Teachers of German of N.Y. and Vicinity (Box 3)
    - see Mankiewicz, Frank, 1936 Feb.
  - Astor National Bank (Box 3)
    - 1900 Aug. 31, 1p
    - 1900 July 7, 1p
  - Astronomical Journal (Box 3)
    see Boss, Benjamin
  - Aswell, E.C. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 27; 1p
  - Atkins, Charles D. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1931 July 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Sept 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Sept 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 July 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 7
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 2; 1p
  - Atkins, J. Brooks (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 1; 1p
  - Atlantic Monthly (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 July 9
    - From Boas, 1920 July 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Dec. 9; 1p
      See Fitzpatrick, T.S.
      See Sedgwick, Ellery
  - Atori, Matilda (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1915 June 11; 1p
  - Auble, John L. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 13; 1p
  - August, V. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 31; 1p
  - Augustin, Johann Jacob (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1926 Aug. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 June 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 21; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 July 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 July 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 4; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 July 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 July 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nove 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept 18; 3p
    - with Heinrich A., 1933 July 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Aug. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Sept. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 21; 1p
    - enc. Burbey, L.H., 1939 May 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 May 15; 1p
    - J.J.A. -- to Krout, J.A., 1941 Sept. 22; 1p
    - J.J.A. -- from Cohen, J., 1941 Oct. 14
    - J.J.A. -- from Burbey, Louis H., 1939 Apr. 28
    - J.J.A. -- from Herskovits, M.J., 1936 Dec. 23
  - Aurivillius, C. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 13; 2p
  - Austen, W. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1918 May 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 May 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1924 May 7; 1p
  - Austin, C.A. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Feb. 6; 1p
  - Austin, Eugenia E. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 24; 2p
  - Austin, W.L. (Box 3)
    - To Benj. Malzberg, 1935 Mar. 4; 2p
  - Austria (Box 3)
    See Ferdinandeum
  - Austria, Minister Plenipotentiary of (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 18; 1p
  - Authors' Guild of America (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1938 May 6; 2p
  - Authors' League of America (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 29; 1p
    - Memorandum, 1938 Mar. 28; 1p
  - Auw. I. von. Jr. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1934 June 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 June 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 June 29; 1p
  - Avalear, F.P. (Box 3)
    - To U.S. Dept. of Justice, 1917 Nov. 1; 2p
  - Averkieva, Julie (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1931 June 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 May 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 25; 1p. On microfilm copy of correspondence, misfiled as May 25, 1932.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 8; 5p
    - To Boas, 1931 Aug. 14; 4p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 5; 5p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 Aug. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 May 10; 1p
  - Avery, George (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1900 Apr. 4
  - Avery, Janet Woolly (Box 3)
    - ToBoas, 1939 Jan. 19; 1p
  - Axebrov. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 14
  - Ayala, R.P. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 31
  - Aydelotte, Cyrus (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1936 May 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 29; 1p
  - Aydelotte, Frank (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1935 Oct. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 June 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1941 June 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 June 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 June 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 June 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 8; 1p
  - Ayer, Ed. E. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 23
  - Ayer, M.A. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1934 June 26; 1p
  - Ayres, E.E. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 25; 1p
  - Ayres, H.M. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 28; 1p
  - Ayres?, John (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 23; 1p
  - AYUDA A MADRID --, 1937 Dec. (Box 3)
  - Azadowskomu, M. (Box 3)
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 8.; 1p
  - Azebrod, A. (Box 3)
    - To Boas, 1900 Mar. 14; 1p